Let me go!
Alaeddin Bey!
Mother..
No...
Mother!
Mother, don't do this! Mother!
Mother! Don't do this to me, mother!
Don't leave your children
motherless and us helpless, mother!
Mother!
Mother! What happened to your hands, mother?
What happened to you? What
did they do to you? Mother...
My Allah, how cruel is this...
How..
Mother! What happened to your
eyes that used to be bright, mother?
What happened mother?
What did they do to you, mother?
How? How?
How did they make the
light in your eyes disappear?
How? How did they do it?
-Who did this?
Who did this?!
Begum Hatun, my Bey.
He is right.
Begum Hatun is responsible for this treachery.
She got on her horse and went that way.
Sister, what did you do?
Begum Hatun, huh?
So...
I will become her hell.
Bala disappeared.
It's like the ground split
open and swallowed her.
But don't worry.
Sofia is also looking for her.
We will surround the forest.
There is no way out for her.
We will find her for sure.
I killed Bala, Ilbay.
-What are you saying, Begum Hatun?
-You heard me. I killed her.
Bala got what she deserved.
Mother!
Mother! What did they do to you?
Bala Hatun!
I could not protect you!
I could not help you!
The pain you caused me...
Now your children will suffer
from the same pain, Bala.
Only your children will get hurt, not me.
Mother..
What kind of pain is this, my Allah?
You're the mountain I'm leaning on.
You're my harbor in my hard times. My sun...
..my moon..
...my day and night...
You are my heart.
You were always with me. Always.
Since the day you said yes
to me, when I swung swords...
...and fought the heathens, I
always had you in my mind.
My strong wife...
All burdens feel lighter with you.
You are my prayer which was answered.
Killing Bala was a mistake.
A mistake?
Bala had long deserved to die.
Remember what happened to Osman.
Should I have let her live and escape?
Once we got Osman, they
both would have died anyway.
Now Osman will attack for revenge.
Osman's heart that burns with the grief of
losing Bala will lead him to make mistakes.
Let him attack. We'll be waiting.
Osman was a dead fire, Begum.
He did not have his Alps and people.
Now, you have revived that fire.
Then I will light a fire for Osman
too, and turn him to ashes in that fire.
Begum!
Nokers(Mongolian soldiers), attack!
Stop him!
You will lose anyway Osman!
You martyred my heart,
my Bala, so treacherously...
Now I will burn you in both worlds.
I will send you seven layers below the earth.
I will not find peace until
I gouge out your eyes.
My sword will find peace only with blood.
I will never stop until I take Bala's revenge.
Nokers(Mongolian soldiers)! Attack!
Ilbay...
So...
...they first captured Osman's Hatun...
...then..
...they let her run away, huh?
It's not just her who ran away, Ulugan.
Bala took Cerkutay and his dog from our hands.
Then let's be thankful, Altuga.
Let's be thankful that Osman's
Hatun hasn't taken our sky from above...
...and the soil from beneath our feet.
Let's be thankful! -Ulugan!
I will slit your throat, Altuga.
I will clean myself with your blood, Altuga.
You were responsible of the tribe's safety.
Even though Ilbay and Begum made a mistake...
...you were the one who was careless.
Quickly! Go after them!
Go support Ilbay!
Kill Cerkutay and his boy.
But I want Osman's wife alive.
Get lost!
We're here, my Bey!
Are you alright?
Let's get out of here. Come on!
Come on, come on.
There is nothing more enjoyable
than watching Turks fighting each other.
You had ruined my plans, Begum.
Now you have to save your filthy life yourself.
The Righteous!
They're going towards the tribe, my Bey.
There are nokers(Mongolian soldiers)
everywhere, my Bey.
Even if they go through the hell gates,
...they can't run away from me.
As they did this to my Bala,
...they will all die! Come on
My silk-haired mother.
My gazelle-hearted mother.
What have they done to you,
mother? They hurt you badly.
They hurt you, mother. Tell
me. What should I do now?
What should I do?
How many lives should I take...
How many states should I destroy to avenge you?
You would tell me...
...that Allah always shows the way.
Tell me now. What should I do, mother?
Where you don't exist isn't home to me.
Where should I go now, mother?
Where should I go, mother? Where?
The fire touched you...
But it's me who burned to ashes, mother.
Your Alaaddin burned to ashes.
How can I endure this, mother?
How can I endure this?
Trails lead to the tribe, my Bey.
Someone's coming, my Bey. Alps!
It's Cerkutay Bey, my Bey.
My Bey.
My Bey, my Bey.
Bala Hatun isn't in the tribe,
my Bey. We escaped, my Bey.
She's with Ghazi and Meryem.
I split up to to distract those jackals, my Bey.
My Bey... My Bey.
Bala Hatun is safe.
Cerkutay Bey.
Mother Bala...
My mother...
...passed away.
No, no.
No, my Shahzade.
What is my Shahzade talking about, my Bey?
Couldn't I protect her?
I couldn't protect... Bala Hatun...Ghazi.
Couldn't I protect Ghazi?
Don't worry, Cerkutay.
Ghazi is alive. He's alright.
I disappointed my Bey.
-Even if Begum Hatun goes to the tribe,
I'll cut off her head!
My Bey, nokers are standing on alert!
Get out of my way, Cerkutay!
My Bey.
-My Bey, no! I can't let you go! Please!
-Cerkutay!
You both disobey me and
stop me from finding Bala's killer!
It's my fault. I couldn't...
I couldn't protect.
It's my fault.
It's my fault. My fault!
You go join Alaaddin.
I'll go after my father.
-It's my fault. I couldn't...
-Cerkutay.
Cerkutay.
Come on, brother. Pull yourself together.
I couldn't protect her.
It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
It was my traitor sister.
Don't blame yourself,
Cerkutay Bey. It's not your fault.
Cerkutay Bey, I know it hurts.
I know the feeling.
But it's not your fault.
Don't be upset.
By rising against those blood suckers
...you did your part, Cerkutay Bey.
I wish my Bey had killed me.
I don't deserve to live.
I don't deserve to live. Get off! Get off!
Don't you hear me?
Don't you see?
It is my fault.
-I couldn't protect her!
-Cerkutay!
Cerkutay, my brother.
Pull yourself together. Enough!
What are you even saying?
I'm saying the right thing.
Saying the right thing!
I say it's not your fault. Don't you get it?
Brother.
-How can I even talk to my Bey again?
-Brother.
Cerkutay, my brother.
-How can I even stand beside him again?
-Cerkutay!
Cerkutay, my brother.
Brother.
Cerkutay, it's the death.
It's the death, brother.
Who can even stand against the death?
Brother, a mortal pen
can't write a person's fate.
It can't.
It's only Allah Who decides, brother.
Pull yourself together. We need to
go now. Pull yourself together, brother.
-It's only Allah Who decides.
-Yes, brother.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, brother. Let's go, alps!
Come on.
My Shahzade.
My Shahzade... My Shahzade...
I wish I had died instead!
I wish!
I wish I were lying down there instead of Bala!
I wish I had died! Not Mother Bala!
I wish I had died instead of Mother Bala!
No more dying, Ghazi.
We will avenge.
We will have our grief.
We will have it, but...
My Shahzade.
The snake called Begum has run off.
Where is Osman Bey?
My Bey's gone.
He was acting weirdly.
We don't know where he's
gone or what he's going to do.
Boran Bey has gone after him just in case.
Fine.
Now..
We're going to Sogut.
Okay, my Shahzade.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate. Don't. Don't.
Nobody will touch her.
I will carry my mother.
I will carry her.
Dastards. Dastards.
You hurt me.
You hurt my heart.
You didn't only take Bala from me..
...but also all my mercy.
What I'm going to do to you
will spread all around the world!
My Bey.
-Son.
No walls..
No shields can stop us from avenging my mother.
But, my Bey... Now...
Now it's time to mourn.
We mourn not by waiting...
...but by vengeance and blood.
You called us here Ulugan.
What do you think you are doing to my Hatun?
-Shut up!
What did you do behind my back, huh?
How did you kill a prisoner...
...under my control? How dare you?
We keep making plans.
We keep making moves,
but we cannot move forward.
I did what needed to be done.
I left Osman helpless.
If there was a man among
you, he would do what I did.
Hatun.
Your hair is long...
...but your mind is short.
You didn't defeat Osman.
You made him more aggressive.
Let him do all he can.
We are here.
You act with the mind of your Hatun.
But let me give you an advice.
What burns quickly burns out quickly.
Osman is a wounded wolf.
A wounded wolf doesn't care about the
hunter behind him or the pain he will feel.
Osman will attack us. He will attack the tribe.
Osman was going to attack
the tribe sooner or later.
He can come, we will resist.
you..
...make a move without informing me again...
...I will take your head before Osman does.
Then what do we have to do?
It's my order.
All the nokers, all your Alps, and even
Sofia's Byzantine soldiers will gather.
If Osman started the war, we will win.
If I am Begum Hatun, just like I took
my revenge from Bala for that slap...
...I will take revenge
from Ulugan as well, Ilbay!
Mother!
Ghazi!
My dear!
Welcome... welcome...
Mother..
They killed Bala Hatun, mother.
What did you say?
Ghazi?
Ghazi, where is my mother?
Ghazi...
What happened?
Is my mother hurt? What happened?
She burned her.
Begum Hatun burned her alive, Gonca Hatun.
No...
Brother?
My Allah...
Mother..
Was this our fate, mother?
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Bala Hatun!
Brother..
Brother... No..
No... Brother..
What is this, brother?
Brother, tell me it's not real. Brother!
Sister...
Brother, no, no, tell me it is not real!
Tell me it's not real... It's not my mother!
No, it's not my mother! It's not!
My Fatma, it's our mother...
No... No... No, no!
No... I'll look! I ll look!
No, don't, Fatma. Don't!
Brother...
Her hand, brother... Her hand, brother!
Brother! Brother!
Her hand!
No, no! Brother!
Brother, no!
No!
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Mother!
My mother is gone... My mother is gone!
O, people!
Sheikh Edebali's daughter...
...Osman Bey's Hatun...
...the glorious mother of all Kayi
My mother...
...Bala Hatun...
...fell a martyr!
Alright, Fatma.
Indeed we belong to Allah...
...and indeed to Him we will return.
Mother!
My Bey...
It's...
...it's my mother's sala.
Brother... -Sister...
Mother! Mother...
Mother!
No...
Mother... mother, come back to me!
Mother, come back!
Brother, save my mother!
Mother..
My heart is burning in flames, brother!
Fatma... Fatma...
My mother is gone... She is gone!
I know sister... I know.
I know.
It will be alright, my Fatma.
It will be alright. -Brother...
It will be alright.. My beautiful sister...
My dear...
Gonca. Holofira.
It will be alright, dear...
You will be alright.
This sorrow..
...this pain destroyed us all.
It left us helpless!
Today...
...is the day of grief for Kayi, people!
Now...
...it's time for Kayis to mourn.
Get ready for the burial.
Once my father comes...
...we will bury my mother.
We will not bury her!
Osman Bey is here.
Father...
Fatma..
Father..
Come on, my beautiful daughter.
Until we take our tribe back...
...we will not bury Bala Hatun.
I will not keep her away...
...from her tribe...
...from her tent..
...from her people and her daughter.
I will say this only once.
And until then..
...until Bala Hatun...
...is buried in the land
where her child rests...
...we will never stop!
Come on!
Walk!
Osman and you...
...will die knowing that
you are nothing before me.
Come on!
All this time...
...I've waited only for this.
Come on!
Get up!
The Kayi's fate is set with sorrow!
The ground threw up killers and
swallowed Bala Hatun instead.
-Our hearts are burned with grief!
-My Allah, what should we do now?
Bala Hatun has gone to heaven.
The cruel are ruling the world!
Shut up!
Shut up
In this tribe, nobody will lament for Bala!
Go away!
-Dastards!
-Vile dogs!
You have no mercy!
Cruel
Whoever can't accept the
endless power of Mongolians...
..will die!
Now go back to your tents.
Or I will bury all of you with Osman's wife!
Osman Bey will make you pay for this.
You think Osman will take revenge? You think so?
I'll take off his mourning heart...
...and make you people eat it!
Dastards!
Vile dogs!
Nokers(Mongolian soldiers) show no mercy!
Leave us!
Dastards!
My Bala.
I knew you wouldn't leave me.
I knew it.
Bala..
Bala...
We shouldn't have got separated like this.
I shouldn't have come to this tree alone.
I should have passed away before you.
Bala.
You devil! Sofia, what's your plan?
-Where are you taking me?
-Move!
Why didn't you leave me?
I'll make you face the hell! I
will make you face the hell!
If I hadn't saved you,
you'd have faced the hell!
You should thank me, shouldn't you?
Poena.
Aunt.
Begum burned the cabin.
Stupid Begum.
How can you stop Osman if you kill Bala?
Stupid!
Bala is burning...
She's dying, aunt.
I won't let her die for now.
If she dies, we can't catch Osman.
Poena, come here!
Take off her clothes.
-Why?
-Hurry up. Poena. Don't ask questions.
Bala!
Bala, come! Come
Come!
I want you to die so much, Bala!
But not now.
Vengeance first.
Bala.
No, Bala. You can't die now.
Bala! Bala!
Bala! Bala?
Sofia.
You owe me a life.
Look.
We'll make Bala put on these.
And make the girl put on Bala's clothes.
-Why?
-To kill Bala.
-They'll think Bala is dead.
-Good, little bird.
Good. Yes.
Come on.
Here.
Poena, go hide.
When Osman comes, tell him Bala is dead.
And blame Begum.
What is your evil plan, huh?
What are you intending to do?
Why didn't you let me die there?
What do you want?
You can't die so easily, Bala.
You haven't tasted the most bitter
grief yet that I prepared for you.
Besides, I'd never let you...
...die without Osman.
I'll kill you myself.
I'll kill you in such a way...
...that you won't be able to escape.
Stop having false hopes, Bala.
Finding out that you're alive,
Osman will fall into my hands.
And I will take unprecedented revenge...
...from you people.
Just a little patience.
Patience.
We still had time.
I should have left this world before you.
Bala. Bala...
They think I'm a tree.
Like this plane tree.
They think I'm a mountain
like those high mountains.
But that mountain was
holding on to another mountain.
You were my mountain.
But the dark mountain has just collapsed.
The strong tree got cut.
My sturdy chest got pierced.
The light enlightening the
dark in my eyes has just died.
It has just died.
Move!
Oh, son..
It's getting dark, father.
It's time for dinner.
Without my mother, though.
Without her voice and smell...
Without mother's wings, father.
Your mother is like a phoenix.
She'll rise from the ashes.
Don't worry. Look.
Just right here. Right here.
How can we endure this suffering, father?
Well..
First, we lost my sister.
Then we lost my unborn baby.
And now mother.
It's like I lose whatever I hold on to.
Son, you should hold on to your cause.
Hold on to your love.
Hold on to life.
Look at me.
We'll avenge your mother.
We will, father.
Move aside!
My lady, Begum Hatun killed Bala...
-Put her in the darkest dungeon.
-Yes, my lady!
Chain her arms and legs!
My lady, everybody thinks Bala is dead.
Because I wanted so.
Osman should burn with
suffering and make a mistake.
Then birds will whisper
to him that Bala is alive.
And Osman will come to his death himself.
What about Ulugan?
Does he know that Bala is...
Whoever isn't loyal to me doesn't know.
And nobody will know.
Uluga
...wants our soldiers to join his nokers.
What do you order about this?
Osman will be overwhelmed by
grief for Bala and attack the tribe.
There will both nokers and us.
So Osman won't be able to run off.
Prepare soldiers immediately
and make them join Ulugan.
I will take his last hope from Osman...
...and play cat and mouse with him.
My Bey.
.we've got the news
...that Byzantine soldiers arrived in
the tribe and joined Ulugan's nokers.
Heathens know...
...Kayis won't stop as Bala Hatun's gone.
They'll look for a corpse to bite off!
Well... What's the situation?
We united our alps in captivity in Sogut
and the alps Yusuf Bey made join us.
All of them are ready to fight now, my Bey.
With the ones we seized in
Sogut, we lack no weapons, my Bey.
You should just give one order for us to
take back the tribe and avenge my mother.
We are ready.
This wild fire burning in our chests...
...is ready for vengeance.
But...
We're outnumbered by
heathens. They are stronger now.
I was going to mention that, my Bey.
How about we wait for some
time to gain more strength?
What are you talking about, Yusuf?
When we performed the
ritual for Bala Hatun outside
...didn't I say that we would never stop?
Before we take back our
tribe and bury Bala Hatun,
...we will never stop.
Even if they are a thousand times
as many as us, we will never stop!
Well..
What bothers me is...
When we want to attack the tribe
...they will try to ambush
us before we reach there.
As we have such a powerful enemy.
...we should be prepared.
Listen carefully now.
Osman is getting ready, Ulugan.
Just as you thought...
Apparently, he will attack the tribe tomorrow.
We need to act fast.
Being fast is for horses.
An eagle waits for the right time.
Are my nokers(Mongolian soldiers) ready, Altuga?
They are all ready to fight, Ulugan.
Our shouts will shake the battlefield.
What about the Byzantines?
Sofia sent all the forces she had.
They are waiting for your order.
Good.
A wolf does not fear an ambush, but...
...it pays its price with its life.
I will cut you into forty pieces, Osman.
Altuga...
At sunrise, you and I will head towards Sogut.
Before Osman reaches the
tribe, we will destroy Sogut.
Then...
We will take Sogut back.
Ilbay...
You will stay here.
If anyone gets past us,
you will protect the tribe.
I will be a shield with my Alps, Ulugan.
Do not worry.
Not only with your Alps...
...you will use all of
Osman's people as a shield.
Tie everyone, children and all, to
stakes and place them on the road.
Do it...
...so Osman cannot shoot arrows...
...or ride his horse.
I will protect the tribe in such a way that...
...Osman will not make a single move.
Do not worry, Ulugan.
I will never give this chair to him.
Come, Osman.
Come.
I still can't believe what happened.
My Allah.
I had no one.
She became my mother.
She never broke my heart.
No one was ever kind to me like her.
May God give us strength.
How is my father?
My father?
Good.
We left him with my mother.
Brother, did my mother suffer a lot?
Fatma...
My mother became a martyr.
She became The Messenger of Allah's...
...neighbour, God willing.
God willing..
God willing, tomorrow,
when we take the tribe back...
...we will bury my mother next to my sister.
At least she will reunite
with her Halime in her grave.
My mother always kept Halime alive.
She searched for my sister
for days, in the water and mud.
Her heart burned from longing and pain.
But my mother always stood strong.
Your sister Halime...
How did she die?
We were children then...
We were not there either.
But I remember how my mother
was as if it were yesterday.
Halime was playing by the stream.
Then she suddenly disappeared.
What happened after that?
For days...
...she searched for my sister in
the water, without eating or drinking.
Then, she found my sister's lifeless body.
My mother never looked the same again.
She never smiled.
Come, my beautiful daughter.
I will check on the sisters.
My daughter, wait for me.
I will come back, alright?
Halime.
Your mother is waiting for you, Halime.
Let go! Let go! Don't touch me!
I said let go! -Bala...
You look good for a dead woman.
Good.
But there is no one left to
take you out of here now.
If I want, I can keep you here for years.
What kind of evil games are you playing now?
No...
Even the devil cannot compete me, Bala.
You never fought bravely,
Sofia. You are just a coward.
No one can make me upset right now, Bala.
I have waited years for this moment.
First you, then Osman. I
will kill you both together.
Never. You will never be able to do that, Sofia.
We have seen many cowards like you.
We defeated all of them
with Allah's permission.
Bala.
I will hurt you so badly that...
Hit me all you want, Sofia!
Because you can only stop
me by chaining my hands!
No, I will not hurt you like that.
I will only...
...tear off the scabs of an old wound.
What are you saying?
I told you about a secret, do you remember?
Bala!
Don't you want to know
the secret I will give you?
Keep your poisonous words to yourself, you
demon! This time, you will not live long.
I will take your life.
What secret, what game
are you talking about Sofia?
I will not fall for your secrets or your games.
Are you sure?
-So you are not curious about who it is about.
-I'm not!
If Halime heard it...
...she would be very sad.
Her mother is not curious
about the secret about her.
You snake! Don't say my daughter's name.
Don't say my daughter's name, Sofia.
My secret is...
..little Halime.
What are you saying, Sofia? Sofia, don't go!
What are you saying, Sofia? Don't
go, come here! Sofia, come here!
What are you saying? Don't
go, come here! Let me go!
Bala..
How many times have I come to this threshold?
How many times have I
turned away from this door?
Seeing you like this.
Seeing you like this
Do you think it is easy for me?
Can Osman stand seeing you like this?
Can he ever stand it?
Your Osman would never leave you alone.
He would never leave you alone.
Bala.
If I can still stand here...
...know that...
...it is only for revenge.
...take you to your daughter Halime.
I will exist only for revenge.
From now on...
...only my sword will speak.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Cerkutay.
-My Bey -Why?
Why weren't you at the council...
...when we were talking
about the attack, Cerkutay?
Why?
My Bey, after my carelessness...
...how could I look at your face?
My Bey, cut my head off.
Take my life.
With your own hands.
I can no longer stand behind you.
I can no longer breathe like this.
I disobeyed your order first.
Then..
Then I couldn't..
...protect Bala Hatun...
...your trust...
...from this fate.
I know this pain, my Bey.
Don't make me live with my head bowed.
Get up.
Get up Cerkutay.
Don't kneel again.
Don't you kneel ever again.
I never had a doubt about
you, even for a moment.
I know...
...you protected Bala...
...that you did your best.
Don't... Don't...
...ever...
...kneel again.
Now you will pull yourself together.
You will become stronger.
You will become stronger so that...
...whoever did this cruelty to us...
...we will make them pay for it.
...my Bey orders.
l am sorry for your loss, my Bey.
-Mother, don't go.
-My Halime, my beautiful daughter.
Your hands touched those herbs,
that's why this soup is delicious.
In the depths of the forest,
a wolf was watching them.
My Halime, my daughter.
Shouldn't I be happy now?
Alaeddin, Fatma, Orhan, Osman..
They all suffer like I did.
But I am also in pain.
Why do I suffer when I see them?
Great Jesus, help me.
Ease my unrest.
God..
God, are you angry with me?
Am I doing a mistake by asking for revenge?
Why?
I suffer when I see them like this. Why?
...suffer even more seeing their pain.
I feel lost
Enlighten my path.
Meryem.
Are you alright?
I was praying for Bala Hatun.
You also loved my mother very
much in a short time, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
She treated me like my own mother.
When I close my eyes, I see
her face instead of my mother's.
That is how my mother is.
She was a mother to everyone.
Meryem.
How did you endure the
pain of losing your mother?
How will I endure my mother's pain?
You will get used to it.
It will burn your heart.
The pain will never disappear.
It will never go away, Fatma Hatun.
It never goes away.
Alaca.
Bala's gone.
You're upset too, right? You are upset.
I will look after you for her now.
I won't leave you.
What's going on? Alaca, calm down.
Alaca, no! Stop!
Alacaz where are you going? Alaca!
Alaca!
Alaca
What's going on?
Alaca!
How?
This is our tree.
Bala's and mine.
Bala.
You're alive. Is this a miracle?
I'm alive, Osman. I'm not dead.
You aren't dead?
Thanks to Allah.
I was waiting for you.
Alaca has brought you to me.
But I knew..
Even if my Brunette Osman were in
his deathbed, he would come for his Bala.
Of course he would.
No matter where he is, he would come.
I would, of course.
I know.
Brunette Osman...
..will never leave his Bala.
I won't.
Bala.
I wish I hadn't opened my eyes.
I wish I had slept...
...for longer.
I wish I had seen you longer.
Bala.
Boran..
-Yes, my Bey?
Any news about Alaca?
Alps looked everywhere,
my Bey. But they couldn't find.
She had a wound, my Bey.
She must have died somewhere.
Dead or alive.
Bring Alaca to me.
As you order, my Bey.
My Allah, You are the
Most Merciful of the merciful.
May You provide peace for my heart.
And foresight for my mind.
Is that snake playing a trick against me again?
I take shelter only in You
and seek help only from You.
Show me the truth, my Allah.
Don't leave me to that demon.
Aameen. Aameen.
My Bey
-What's the situation, my Bey?
-The intel turned out to be true.
Ulugan made Byzantine heathens
join his nokers and is coming to Sogut.
What is their formation? Did you observe?
They' took a formation not to
be seen while approaching Sogut.
Countless dogs are walking in one single line.
They're coming through narrow passages.
Just like I predicted.
It's happening as I predicted.
Shahzades will move in
one wing and we in the other.
We'll hit them unexpectedly.
Come on!
We'll advance silently...
...and stand against Osman like the death
Ulugan, we are so many...
...that the back side
are just leaving the tribe.
Osman has no chance.
Osman has left Sogut, Commander
Ulugan. He's coming here.
-How many alps does Poor Osman have?
-Just a few.
They can never challenge
your mighty army, Ulugan.
A Bey spreads his reputation
around the world, but...
...he makes a mistake due to a hatun
...gets ambitious and loses.
Nokers, today is the day of fight!
To paint these lands with
blood and slaughter alps today
...move forward
Leave me!
You dastard!
Tie this dog's hands!
Leave! Leave me!
Leave me!
This is the punishment of those
who lament for our enemies...
...and who try to protect them!
-Leave me.
-If Osman attempts to attack,
...he'll hit the ones loyal to him.
You traitors! You betrayed Kayi!
You betrayed your own kin!
You serve Mongolians!
I'm not doing this to you! Osman is!
If you see Osman as the head
instead of me, I will crush all your heads!
You betrayed Kayi!
You traitor dog!
Dastard!
Mine too, Ilbay Bey? Will you crush my head too?
Ayse, didn't I tell you not to leave the tent?
You think I will ignore your cruelty?
Never!
-I will resist with people!
-Go inside, Ayse.
-Tie me here!
-Take her to the tent.
Traitor! You betrayed Kayi!
Dog of Mongolians!
If you don't obey me, you can't exist!
You should know that!
-Shame on you.
-You betrayed Kayi.
Halime.
My daughter.
You are curious, huh?
I knew, Bala.
I know you very well.
What did you mean?
What did you mean? What
secret? My deceased daughter...
Sofia.
I came back long time ago. You know that, Bala?
I saw your daughter.
Was it you who killed her?
Did you kill her, Sofia?
If so, I will kill you terribly!
Am I such a person?
I came back to help you meet your daughter.
What do you mean?
Are you playing with my mind, Sofia?
Your daughter is alive, Bala.
Halime is alive.
My daughter is dead,
Sofia! You're lying! Go away!
Get out of here!
You're lying!
Go! Go!
Your daughter.
Your daughter...
...loves eating apples, right?
And she's very fond of her damn father.
Look, Bala.
Do you remember?
How did you get that?
How did you get that talisman, Sofia?
-How did you get that?
-It's Halime's talisman, right?
No, Sofia. Give it to me.
How did you get that,
Sofia? How did you get that?
I've been..
I've been waiting for this moment, Bala.
Sofia! Give it to me!
How did you get that? No! No!
Like my father said.
...they are moving like a snake.
Byzantine soldiers and Mongolians...
While walking through this route,
While walking through this route.
...they will follow this thin path.
They'll move like a snake here.
But the snake will be so long
...that the head won't realize...
...when we cut off the tail.
While Ulugan goes in the front.
...we'll start attacking.
We will divide them first.
We'll tear them apart slowly.
Alaaddin, you got my back.
Saruca, you get the end of the tail.
Here we go. May Allah bless our fight.
Let's go.
For vengeance, attack!
-Allah is the greatest!
Come on, alps!
-Show no mercy! Allah is the greatest!
-Ya Allah!
In the name of Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Come on
Come on! We'll join Alaaddin Bey.
-Come on, Alps!
-Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest!
I swear I'll kill all of you. All of you!
Ulugan's army must have
scattered by now, my Bey.
Ulugan won't live for long.
He will wait for his death now.
Ulugan dog thinks we will face him.
But with Allah's permission,
we will take our tribe back.
We will.
Sure we will.
They are using the innocent people
as shields at the gates, my Bey.
Right.
Now they think we will come through the gate.
But Turks are wolves.
They are as sharp as swords.
We will attack them from
where they least expect.
Archers!
Once the sword is drawn from its sheath...
...it is never put back in it without bloodshed.
Wolves have now risen.
Now..
Now, these infidels will only see blood...
...they won't see another day. Don't...
Don't hurt the people.
With Allah's permission, my Bey.
Archers!
Shoot!
Come on valiants! Kill
all the infidels! Ya Allah!
Attack!
What do you mean Sofia?
Is Halime alive, huh?
Why do you... Why do you have
that jawshan? Tell me something
Sofia, talk to me! Is Halime alive?
Tell me! Is she alive?
Talk to me Sofia!
She is alive.
I kidnapped her Bala.
I raised her like my own daughter...
...like a Christian.
You..
You...
...prevented the possibility
of me having children.
And I took your child!
And you...
...have cried for years at the
grave of a child you never knew.
Snake! Snake!
And I...
...killed you while you were alive, Bala.
While you were alive...
I will kill you!
I will tear out the heart of
anyone who touches my child.
How could you touch my gazelle-eyed daughter?
How could you touch her?
I will kill you, Sofia.
I will kill you.
Tell me, what did you do to her?
Tell me! What did you do to my daughter?
What did you do to her?!
Tell me!
Don't touch! Stay away!
Sofia
Let go! Sofia!
I will kill you with my bare hands, Sofia!
I will make you pay for the pain you caused!
I will make you pay for it, Sofia!
Let go!
Poena is here, ma'am. She is waiting for you.
Have a good rest, Bala.
When I return...
...we will continue our story, huh?
-You won't leave.
-Look at this carefully.
Am I telling the truth, huh?
Let her look at this carefully.
Sofia. Don't go! Give that to me!
Sofia.
You won't leave! Sofia come here! Sofia!
Halime..
Halime... No... no..
She is lying... She is lying...
My Halime...
It's really you, my daughter.
My Allah... Keep me sane...
My Halime...
You are alive, my daughter.
You are alive, my dear...
Where are you? Where are you, my Halime?
I will find you.
I will take you. I will find you.
Our way leads to victory...
...and we are called victors! Alps!
Kill them with your dark
steel! Allah is the Greatest!
Allah is the Greatest!
It's a game.
Osman lured us into a trap.
I was waiting for you, dastards.
Come closer..
Come..
...get your share...
...from this dark sword.
Don't let any of them survive. Kill them all!
Come on! Move!
Come on Alps!
My Shahzade...
We need to go and help Orhan Bey.
-Now it is time to unite.
-Thank Allah.
You are right.
You are right
brothers. Come on then!
Come on!
What is that, dog Altuga?
You are scared like you see
the Azrael when you see me.
Orhan, your mother was burned alive but...
...you still don't know what pain is.
But I will teach you.
Osman is not around Commander Ulugan.
So you played a game, Osman.
You made us think you were
here, and now you'll attack the tribe.
The head of the snake is here.
Turhan.
Ya Allah.
Do not let these dogs survive! Come on! Nokers!
We are going to the tribe.
Demon... He realized it was a game.
We need to inform my father immediately.
-Alaeddin Bey...
I'll go.
Even if something happens to me...
-...I will be thankful.
-Thank you, Saruca. Go now.
Go after him!
Don't let him go to the tribe!
Get on your horses nokers! Come on!
Come on brothers! Attack!
Ya Allah!
I will slit your throat. Come at me, you dog.
You attacked my tribe!
You tortured my people!
I will drown you in your own blood!
Kill them, valiants!
Kill the dastard dogs and
send them away from our tribe!
Allah is the Greatest!
-For the revenge...
...of our Beys, our Alps...
...and for our martyrs! For freedom
For The Righteous!
Attack!
A Turk is worth a thousand jackals. Come, come!
Come, come!
I am coming, my Bey! I am coming!
Poena.
Why did you come here? -I don't know aunt.
I don't feel alright.
That family is making me feel this way.
What is wrong? Did something happen?
What is happening. Poena?
Did my mother ever cook Turkish food?
What does that mean?
I don't know, maybe she did.
Why are you asking me this?
I don't know. I don't know anything.
I am confused.
A smell, a moment...
It feels like I'm remembering
a moment I never lived.
It feels like I'm not the
person in those dreams.
Have you..
...not slept enough lately Poena?
Was my father playing games with me?
Sure..
...my little bird.
Your father, your mother..
...was taking good care of you...
...and doing everything for you.
You answer my question.
Did you drink the syrup I brought?
No, it broke before I could drink it.
Damn it. Poena.
I told you not to neglect it.
I'm sorry aunt, I...
...dropped it in that chaos.
It's not important my little bird...
...I am just worried about you.
Wait...
Here. Take it.
Take it regularly.
Keep it with you.
Once you get a good sleep,
everything will be alright.
What is Osman doing?
I don't know.
Everyone is devastated.
That's why I could easily come here.
They will get even more upset.
Come on.
Go now.
Is Bala alive, aunt?
You will kill her.
She is in the dungeon now.
-Can I see her?
-No, not now.
Come on. Go. Go.
I'll see Bala, aunt.
Come on!
Come to me, Ilbay.
If you don't care about yourself,
care about your people, Osman.
Drop your sword and surrender.
Turn around and look.
Come on!
Osman.
Your tribe will be your grave.
Your people and alps will
water your grave with their blood.
My nokers
We'll destroy Osman and his tribe.
We'll sow the seeds of eternal fear! Here we go!
My Halime drowned.
She drowned. How is this...
How? She drowned.
You have to tell me everything
Sofia. Tell me everything.
My Halime drowned.
I buried her with my hands. I don't believe you.
-Speak!
-Bala.
You are underestimating me.
Tell me everything, Sofia!
It was a time of war. You
were fighting in different parts.
I heard that you would go help the migrants.
It was the most suitable time.
You were going for help
when I attacked your caravan.
You couldn't have taken Halime with you.
-Ulgen Hatun, help me!
-My Allah!
While my servants were
stalling Ulgen, I took Halime.
You snake! You demon!
You know the rest.
For ten days,
...I watch you suffering, Bala.
Then...
I sent you a little girl looking like Halime.
She got swollen due to water.
You couldn't have recognized her.
Sofia, where is my daughter?
Where is my daughter? Tell me where she is!
I'll kill you, Sofia. I will kill you.
I will kill you!
Sofia, where is daughter?
Tell me where she is!
Tell me!
Finally, it's time to kill you, Osman.
Since the day I joined you, I've
always dreamed of this moment.
You aren't the first traitor who was one of us.
It's a pity that I will have my uncle
Sungur Tegin's blood on my hands.
You said you were a Kayi.
Your betrayed your own kin.
You aren't a Kayi at all.
You're the dark sheep of Kayi!
You say fancy words to cover your
weakness, but it doesn't affect me!
It will! I will take your life!
I will also cut
Begum into pieces!
Come to me.
Come on, come on, sisters!
-Move!
-Move, move!
What? What?
-My Bey!
-What is it?
What is it? Are my sons alright?
-My Bey...
Our plan got ruined. Ulugan is coming, my Bey.
-They are too many.
-What are you saying?
Saruca!
Osman!
Whoever protects you will
drown in their own blood, Osman.
You heathen dog!
You have a death wish, huh?
You thought you could fool me?
You were wrong!
Alps! Defending formation!
Alps!
Nokers, burn them!
-Split up -Come on!
My Bey.
-Osman Bey has fallen!
Our Bey has fallen!
Our Bey has fallen
Osman Bey hasn't fallen but died!
My Bey.
My Bey, are you alright?
They are too many, my Bey.
Alps are dying one by one.
-Come on! Gather now. -We couldn't make it.
Gather, alps!
Follow me, come on!
Come on, brothers!
You can't run away from me in this world, Osman.
Nokers, go after them. Go!
Come on, come on.
-Cerkutay!
-Allah!
Let's go!
Let's go.
I will kill you, Sofia. Where is my daughter?
She always waited for
you, her brothers and father.
But you didn't come.
While Halime was crying
...you didn't come, Bala.
She was just little.
My precious angel was just little.
Just little, Sofia
Bala.
Yes, she was.
So it was easier.
I took everything from...
...your little angel.
Her name. Her memories and everything.
Halime..
My baby...
Halime doesn't know you, Bala.
Halime..
...is my girl now.
My baby...
She is my girl.
Hold on, brave man. We'll
check your wound. Alps!
Set the fire!
-My Bey.
-My brave man. Hold on.
Saruca... Saruca?
Time is up for me, my Bey.
I feel the fire in my chest.
-No.
No way! No way, brave man.
This wound can't kill you.
This pain...
It's different, my Bey.
I can feel it.
This is the death.
My Bey, my father Bayhan Bey used to say...
A brave man shows himself in the hard times.
Have I ever left you in a hard time, my Bey?
No.
You have never left me alone in hard times.
You've always gone first for me.
I'm pleased with you.
Thank Allah.
The fire in my chest is gone now, my Bey
I've heard these words from you.
So I can die gladly now.
My Bey.
I have a request from you.
Tell me.
I'm ready to do anything no matter what.
This is my father's hat. You gave me this.
My Bey.
Make them bury me beside my father.
Help me meet my father.
This warrior should be with his father.
I will find peace there.
God willing.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
...and I bear witness that
Muhammad(PBUH) is His servant...
...and Messenger.
Indeed we belong to Allah,
and indeed to Him we will return.
Alps. You will fulfill his last wish.
My Bey.
Come on!
What are you doing here, Boran
Bey? Where is my father going?
We couldn't succeed, my Shahzade.
We did our best, but we failed.
We were about to take our tribe back.
Ulugan dog came.
They all came back.
Why are you standing there? What happened?
Wait, Shamil. Stop.
Brother... Brother... Saruca
Saruca.
Who did this?
Cerkutay Bey!
-We could not take our tribe.
Saruca...
...became a martyr.
And my Bey left.
I will take your revenge.
I will.
I swear, I will make them pay
for what they did to you, brother.
...the Ruler of the skies and the ground!
My Allah, I opened my hands
My Allah, please do not reject me...
Please do not reject me.
You ordered..
My Allah... I always trusted You.
I have always prayed to You!
May You... enlighten my way. May
You accept my prayers, my Allah...
May You accept my prayers...
Alaca.
Alaca. What happened?
Is it..
Is it good news? Is it, my girl?
Huh, Alaca?
What is happening to you?
Alaca, calm down! Alaca! Stop!
Stop! Alaca! Where are you going? Alaca!
Alaca..
You are sad because Bala is gone, right?
Your wings are broken.
And my arms are broken.
Right...
You are right.
Alaca!
Iltutan!
Where is Alaca going? Go after her! Alaca!
Alaca..
Alaca?
My dark Osman...
...never leaves his Bala alone.
Bala..
Alaca, is
Is it..
Is it good news?
Is she...
Is Bala alive?